{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080219756","data":{"timestamp":" 947080219755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" ec583458-7065-4d20-966c-4110c2461c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080224961","data":{"timestamp":" 947080224961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" ec583458-7065-4d20-966c-4110c2461c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080227791","data":{"timestamp":" 947080227790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" ec583458-7065-4d20-966c-4110c2461c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080239685","data":{"timestamp":" 947080239685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080243852","data":{"timestamp":" 947080243851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080245435","data":{"timestamp":" 947080245435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080250198","data":{"timestamp":" 947080250198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080251790","data":{"timestamp":" 947080251790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080256148","data":{"timestamp":" 947080256148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080257756","data":{"timestamp":" 947080257756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080261904","data":{"timestamp":" 947080261904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080263547","data":{"timestamp":" 947080263547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080267426","data":{"timestamp":" 947080267425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080269041","data":{"timestamp":" 947080269040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080273322","data":{"timestamp":" 947080273322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080274929","data":{"timestamp":" 947080274928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080279114","data":{"timestamp":" 947080279113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080280722","data":{"timestamp":" 947080280721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080284653","data":{"timestamp":" 947080284652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080286248","data":{"timestamp":" 947080286248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080289680","data":{"timestamp":" 947080289680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080291275","data":{"timestamp":" 947080291275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080295514","data":{"timestamp":" 947080295514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080297076","data":{"timestamp":" 947080297076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080300682","data":{"timestamp":" 947080300682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080302692","data":{"timestamp":" 947080302691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080302852","data":{"timestamp":" 947080302852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" db70e6a8-af4f-4ee3-9f91-dca599a55512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083730036","data":{"timestamp":" 947083730035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083737422","data":{"timestamp":" 947083737421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083739023","data":{"timestamp":" 947083739022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083742689","data":{"timestamp":" 947083742689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083744259","data":{"timestamp":" 947083744259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083748828","data":{"timestamp":" 947083748827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083750428","data":{"timestamp":" 947083750427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083754595","data":{"timestamp":" 947083754594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083756209","data":{"timestamp":" 947083756209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083760204","data":{"timestamp":" 947083760204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083761763","data":{"timestamp":" 947083761763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083765738","data":{"timestamp":" 947083765738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083767319","data":{"timestamp":" 947083767318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083772303","data":{"timestamp":" 947083772302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083773857","data":{"timestamp":" 947083773857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083778564","data":{"timestamp":" 947083778564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083780127","data":{"timestamp":" 947083780127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083783481","data":{"timestamp":" 947083783480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083785085","data":{"timestamp":" 947083785084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083789093","data":{"timestamp":" 947083789093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083790686","data":{"timestamp":" 947083790685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083794182","data":{"timestamp":" 947083794182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083796203","data":{"timestamp":" 947083796202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083796362","data":{"timestamp":" 947083796361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 6b8ae779-77cf-4356-a44d-49e639c5d76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083806019","data":{"timestamp":" 947083806019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 76b952bd-d16b-4ebf-abc8-f8c157534d05"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083806241","data":{"timestamp":" 947083806241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 76b952bd-d16b-4ebf-abc8-f8c157534d05"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083806996","data":{"timestamp":" 947083806996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 76b952bd-d16b-4ebf-abc8-f8c157534d05"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083807081","data":{"timestamp":" 947083807081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 76b952bd-d16b-4ebf-abc8-f8c157534d05"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083814441","data":{"timestamp":" 947083814441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 76b952bd-d16b-4ebf-abc8-f8c157534d05"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083831242","data":{"timestamp":" 947083831242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" e44250f2-9a65-4dc1-9bff-a782ecbb858c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083840999","data":{"timestamp":" 947083840999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" e44250f2-9a65-4dc1-9bff-a782ecbb858c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083842858","data":{"timestamp":" 947083842857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" e44250f2-9a65-4dc1-9bff-a782ecbb858c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083859958","data":{"timestamp":" 947083859957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_baba-watoto-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083862646","data":{"timestamp":" 947083862645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_baba-watoto-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083871397","data":{"timestamp":" 947083871397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083879213","data":{"timestamp":" 947083879213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_kaka-mama-watoto-baba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083885621","data":{"timestamp":" 947083885621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083886237","data":{"timestamp":" 947083886236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083894076","data":{"timestamp":" 947083894075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mjoma_watoto-mwanafunzi-mjoma-babu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083905085","data":{"timestamp":" 947083905085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083917102","data":{"timestamp":" 947083917102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083924661","data":{"timestamp":" 947083924660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083930068","data":{"timestamp":" 947083930068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083934779","data":{"timestamp":" 947083934778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083936737","data":{"timestamp":" 947083936735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083943233","data":{"timestamp":" 947083943233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 1b436155-0086-43c1-8c01-03770bf68350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083963768","data":{"timestamp":" 947083963768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyayo_nyayo-vidole-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyayo"," userResponse":" nyayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083978080","data":{"timestamp":" 947083978080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tumbo_tumbo-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083985332","data":{"timestamp":" 947083985331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bega_mguu-nyayo-bega"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bega"," userResponse":" bega"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947083994519","data":{"timestamp":" 947083994519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kichwa_vidole-kichwa-pua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084000620","data":{"timestamp":" 947084000619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pua_pua-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pua"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084010067","data":{"timestamp":" 947084010067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_mguu-bega-meno"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084020700","data":{"timestamp":" 947084020700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkono_tumbo-mkono-mdomo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084027260","data":{"timestamp":" 947084027260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_jicho-mdomo-mkono"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084033962","data":{"timestamp":" 947084033962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_mguu-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084041740","data":{"timestamp":" 947084041740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_mguu-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084051904","data":{"timestamp":" 947084051904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_mdomo-meno-jicho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" mdomo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084058804","data":{"timestamp":" 947084058804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_mdomo-meno-jicho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084064567","data":{"timestamp":" 947084064566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" 2376faae-c144-4012-ab8c-cc10d05c26a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_mdomo-meno-jicho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084082118","data":{"timestamp":" 947084082118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" ac4347cc-7b29-4395-9327-e570b6b1a44d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084088594","data":{"timestamp":" 947084088594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" ac4347cc-7b29-4395-9327-e570b6b1a44d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084094418","data":{"timestamp":" 947084094418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_165005"," gameId":" ac4347cc-7b29-4395-9327-e570b6b1a44d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}